Did you know there are two ways to
midi-learn your faders in blackout? So
let's learn about it.
So on my fader page, if I go to link
status, connect to device and midi-learn,
I can begin to learn my faders. This
globe icon up at the top, this is our
magic button. This is
our global versus local mode. If I tap an
unassigned fader and then all I have to
do is move the fader
I want to assign it to and it learns just
like that. You'll see at
the top it's telling me that
it's a global fader. So if I leave
midi-learn now and switch to page two, I
still have control. And
if I switch back to page one, I still
have control. But now let's see what
happens when we learn it as
a local fader. I'll go back into
midi-learn and now I'll click the globe
to learn it as a local
fader. I'll click an empty fader, go
ahead and learn it. I love
how easy that is and I'll
override it. And you can see that it's
actually learning fader one
on page one. So now you'll see
here I still have control of this fader.
But if I switch to page
two, I'm not controlling it
anymore. I'm still controlling the fader
on page one. So if I bring
this to full, when I switch
back to page one, you'll see it's at
full, bring it down to zero, it's at
zero, and it's not affecting
page two. So that's your quick tip of the
day. This is super useful
for customizing your setup
the way that you want, whether you're
running a time code show
with midi or you're just setting
up your fader board. Lots
of options here in blackout.